[Music]
Meta fields are a flexible way to add
and store additional information about
Shopify resources such as a customer or
company. You can synchronize and then
manage meta fields in the business
central either via UI or via
extensibility model where you can map
meta fields to business central fields
or other entities. Let's see the demo.
You see the custom data in Shopify being
extended by using metap fields.
import that customer from Shopify into
Business
Central. You can get access to review
meta fields from a list where you can
open card and the same action is
available there as well. When opened,
you can see all meta fields of various
types including the one of type customer
reference. Developers can map standard
or custom fields and related entries in
Business Central to Shopify meta fields
using an extensibility model. Code
samples are available in the
documentation. These fields are
non-editable because synchronization is
from Shopify. For B2B companies,
synchronization is not for all companies
and the can update Shopify companies
toggle is
on. Data entry can be performed
here. Metap field definitions created by
administrators in Shopify are shown in
the Shopify company card for easy data
entry. In this release, we can import
meta field definitions requiring only
the input of necessary data.
The enter data is now available in
Shopify. Thank you for watching. You can
find more details about capability in
the release note. Also watch other
videos about enhancements on Shopify
connector. You can find links in the
description.